

+972-50-4972328 |yuriyzdev@gmail.com | GitHub | LinkedIn

Professional Summary

Full Stack engineer with experience in video game development and music production.



Technical Skills

Front-end: HTML, CSS (including Bootstrap), JavaScript (ES6), React, React Native, Angular.

Back-end: NodeJS, Express, SQL, MongoDB, Firebase, Heroku (Dyno), AWS, Serverless.

Other relevant skills: REST APIs, Unit-Testing, Git, C#, Unity, TypeScript.

Education

2021-2021 Full-stack Coding Bootcamp, Israel Tech Challenge (ITC).

3-month full-time intensive training bootcamp focused on web development, using the latest languages and frameworks followed by a 2-month project in a high-tech company.

2019-2020 Video Game Development, Sv College.

6 Month course for video game development in Unity 3D & 2D.

The course covers usage of the Unity software, game design and scripting in C#.

Game developer certificate.

2014-2017 Music Production and Sound Design, BPM College.

3 Year course for music production and sound design (music theory, Ableton, Cubase, Synthesis).

Sound engineer certificate.

Work Experience

2020-2022 Full stack engineer, TLVTech.

- Working as part of the client's product team.
- Implementation of new features\Improvement of existing features.
- Server maintenance.
- Main tools\stack: NodeJS, AWS, Serverless, 3rd party API's, React Native.

2021-Present **Full stack Engineer**, Freelance.

- Wide variety of work from building a single website to creating rest API servers, bots and video games.
- Work with different technologies and services some of which are AWS, Telegram, Unity3D and more.
- Creation and maintenance of web applications and services.

Military Service

2012-2014 **Sergeant, Air Force,** Military photographer.

- Documenting events, military practices and special PR visits.
- Writing, editing and publishing weekly newsletter.
- Managing events planned by the operating office.

Additional Information

• Spoken languages: English (Fluent), Hebrew (Native) Russian (Native).